Some of you may be thinking, why do you need state management?
After all, you have the power of composables.
Who needs it anymore?
I can do everything. We don't need state management stores.
Yes, it is true. We basically model how data source work,
you basically are doing your state, your getters, your actions.
The thing I always tell people about state management libraries
is that what you're providing your team is a set of standards that everyone can follow.
Now granted, if you're going to author your own internal state management library
that you heavily document and that's type-save and if you want to do all that,
that is awesome and I like more power to you.
But one of the things that things like Piniad does allow us to do
is the fact that you have these full-time open source maintainers
who are basically trying to create the, especially within the view community,
they're very motivated to create the best UX they can give you.
And so, for example, you can see here in the new DevTools,
let's see, here's like the little Piniad icon, what pineapple.
You can see here, you can actually see all the stuff, you can inspect it,
you can even modify it, if you need to test anything, save it down.
It can even track the timeline in terms of mutations. So, I believe
if I went in here and changed this,
yeah, I guess you were quite up big task.
Oh, oh, I think I didn't know why, that one's not connected yet.
But you can see here, basically, there,
you get a lot of this work for free.
And to be honest, if you look underneath Piniad in particular,
it's really not that far from composable. It's just a set of standards that's kind of been
agreed upon by the community. So, if you're worried about like bulk in that kind of stuff,
Piniad has already, unlike for those of us who were in the UX days, the view too,
that was heavier. Because a lot of times,
you had to do a lot to manually optimize the performance of it.
So, back then, a lot of people would use global stores, basically, one big store,
and they would chunk out small stores. But what they didn't know was that all the
sorts of being lumped in together. So, anytime someone loaded something, they were loading.
It was the whole like, assorably, and I got to get the rainforest kind of thing.
And so, Piniad, by default, every time we do something,
like we see here where we just do like a test store, time entry store,
those are already tree shaken, they're separate. They're basically equivalent of these
composables we have here where as long as you're importing them on specific files,
like it's already doing that for you. There's no like giant glob that's being built together
and then being shipped through users. And so, for that reason, I find that generally speaking,
state management libraries are helpful for especially large teams. Teams that need some standards.